Guide to the Business Office, Yale School of Drama, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Business Office, 1956-1982; Accession 1986-A-026
  - Surveys: Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 498)
  - Synagogue, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 499)
  - T Correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box 25, Folder 500)
  - "Tartuffe", 1966 (Box 25, Folder 501)
  - Taxes, Federal: W-2, W-3, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 502)
    - Quarterly Returns (Box 25, Folder 503)
  - Taxes: Internal Revenue and Labor Department (Unemployment: State of Connecticut), undated (Box 25, Folder 504)
  - Taxes, State, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 505)
    - 1968 (Box 26, Folder 506)
  - Taxes, State, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 507)
    - 1970 (Box 26, Folder 508)
  - Taxes, State Quarterly, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 509)
  - Taxes, State Unemployment, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 510)
  - Technical Department, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 512)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 513)
  - Technical Production and Theatre Administration Programs, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 514)
  - Telephone Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 26, Folder 516)
  - Telephone Credit Cards, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 517)
  - Telephone Expenses, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 518)
  - Telephone: Invalid Tolls, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 519)
    - New Yale Toll System, 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 520)
  - Telephone Statements, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 521)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 522)
  - Theatre Administration, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 523)
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 524)
    - Students, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 525)
  - Theatre Communications Group, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 526)
    - Annual Fiscal Survey, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 527)
    - Conference, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 528)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 529)
    - National Working Conference: Robert J. Orchard, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 530)
  - Theatre Communications Group: Newsletter, 1975-1977 (Box 27, Folder 531)
    - Observership Program, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 532)
  - Theatre Curtains, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 533)
  - Theatre Design and Lighting Department, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 534)
  - Theatre of the Deaf, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 535)
  - "The Three Sisters": Box Office Statements, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 536)
  - Ticket Donations, 1974-1977 (Box 27, Folder 537)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 538)
    - 1979-1981 (Box 27, Folder 539)
  - Ticket Policies, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 540)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 541)
    - 1977 (Box 28, Folder 542)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 543)
    - 1979-1981 (Box 28, Folder 544)
  - Ticket Privileges, 1973-1975 (Box 28, Folder 545)
  - Ticket Reservation System, Inc. (TRS), 1968 (Box 28, Folder 546)
  - "Tis Pity She's a Whore": Box Office Statements, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 547)
  - Touring Companies, 1973-1977 (Box 28, Folder 548)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 549)
  - Trinity Square Repertory Company, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 550)
  - Truck, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 551)
  - Typesetting, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 552)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 553)
  - Undergraduate Employment, 1973-1975 (Box 28, Folder 554)
  - United Way Campaign, 1974-1977 (Box 28, Folder 555)
  - United Way Campaign, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 556)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 557)
  - Unit Set Photographs, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 558)
  - University Council: Committee on Drama, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 559)
  - University Matters, 1972-1976 (Box 28, Folder 560)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 29, Folder 561)
  - University Theatre: Electrical System, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 562)
    - Floor Plans, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 563)
    - Requests, 1972-1977 (Box 29, Folder 564)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 565)
  - Ushering, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 566)
    - 1977 (Box 29, Folder 567)
  - Usher Problems, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 568)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Box 29, Folder 569)
  - "Vampire" Workshop 4: Box Office Statements, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 570)
  - Vehicle and Truck Matters, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 571)
  - Vehicles, 1966-1970 (Box 29, Folder 572)
  - Velour Inventory, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 573)
  - "Victor", 1967 (Box 29, Folder 575)
  - The Vienneau Concert Ballet, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 576)
  - "Viet Rock": Production Costs, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 577)
  - "Volpone": Contracts, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 578)
    - Production Costs, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 579)
  - W Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 580)
  - "We Bombed in New Haven": Box Office Statements, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 583)
  - What Color Goes with Brown?, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 584)
  - "Who Am I?": Receipts, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 585)
  - Weekly Press Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 586)
  - WNHC Building, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 589)
  - Women's Liaison Committee: Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 590)
  - Workshops, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 591)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 592)
  - Work Study, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 593)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 594)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 595)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 30, Folder 596)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 597)
  - "Woyzeck", 1971 (Box 30, Folder 599)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous, 1974-1977 (Box 30, Folder 600)
  - "X" Workshop 6, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 601)
  - Yale-ABC Playwriting.Program, 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 602)
  - Yale Cabaret, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 603)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 604)
    - 1972 (Box 30, Folder 605)
  - Yale Cabaret: Expenses, 1972-1977 (Box 30, Folder 606)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 607)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 30, Folder 608)
    - Expenses, 1979-1983 (Box 30, Folder 609)
  - Yale Concert Dancers, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 610)
  - Yale Inter-Office Correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 30, Folder 611)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 612)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre: Alternate Locations, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 613)
    - Associate Artists (YRTAA), 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 614)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 31, Folder 615)
    - Box Office, undated (Box 31, Folder 616)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 31, Folder 617)
    - Financial Status, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 618)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973-1979 (Box 31, Folder 619)
    - 780B Accounts, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 620)
  - Yale/Theatre Magazine, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 621)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 622)
    - 1977 (Box 31, Folder 623)
  - Yale University Memos, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 624)
  - Yale University Press, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 625)
  - York University, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 626)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 627)
  - Budgetary Footnotes: Faculty Salaries, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 628)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 629)
  - Salaries, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 630)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 631)
- Records of the Business Office, 1983-1987; Accession 1989-A-027
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  - Budget Print-outs, 1985-1986
    - Inventory 780R, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Gifts, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Special Use, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Accounting Transfers, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 780D, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 780B, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 780H, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Grants, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Endowment, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Ends, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 780C, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Facilities, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Theatre Mag Cabaret, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Limited Use, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Our Print-outs 780A, 780B, 780C, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - GA Summary, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Concession Cash Receipt Journals, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Invoices
    - A (general), 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Ace Sewing Machine, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Actor's Equity Association, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Ads, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Advanced Business Computers, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Advocate, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Alcone, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Apartment, 84 Howe St., # 612, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Apartment, 84 Howe St., # 300, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Apartment, 202 Park St., # 3, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Automatic Data Processing of New England, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - B (general), 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Bachman Distributors, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Baloo Enterprises Ltd., 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Blooms, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - B.N. Productions, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Bridge Haven Ford Truck Sales, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Brown, James and Sons, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Budget Rent-A-car/Truck, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - C (general), 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Cabaret, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - The Carpet Shop, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - The Camera Shops, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Charm's Hardware, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Chapel Wine, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Chapin and Bangs, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Charrette, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Coastal Tool Supply, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Cobb's Stationary, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Coe and Brown, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Colony Inn, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Box Folder, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Colton, Weissber, Hartnick, Yamin and Sherensky, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Commission on the Deaf, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Comp One, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Computer Center, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Conn. Bar and Restaurant, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Conn. Fountain Syrup Co., 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Conn. Plumbing Supply, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Conn. Plywood, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Continental Lumber, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Country Harbors, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - County Mailing Service, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Credit Card Usage, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Custom Food Service Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Cylinder Rent, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - D (general), 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Dazian's, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Devoe and Reynolds, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Dichello Distributors, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Drama Productions, Inc. First Quarter 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Drama Productions, Inc. Second Quarter 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Drama Productions, Inc. Third Quarter 1985, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Drama Productions, Inc. Fourth Quarter 1985, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Doufast, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - E (general), 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Eagle Leasing, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - F (general), 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Federal Express, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - For Art's Sake, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Foxon Lumber, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - S.Z. Field, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - G (general), 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - GandG Distributors, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - General Wine and Liquor, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Gnomon Copy, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Good Copy, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Golden Crest Farms, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Gothic Color, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - W. Grainger, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Grand Light and Supply, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Great Bear Spring, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Greenberg and Hammer, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - H (general), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Hartford Cordage, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Harvard Business School, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Harty Electronics, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Horowitz Brothers, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Howard Arnold, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Hull's Hobbies, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Internal Revenue Service, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Industrial Safety Supply, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Iggie's Saw Shop, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Instantwhip, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Insurance, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Inventory, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - J (general), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Jamco Electronics, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Jo-Ev Cleaners, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - K (general), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Kaye's Art Shop, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Kinko's Copies, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Knox Norton, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Koeing, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Kops Monahan Travel, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - L (general), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Lasalle Audio, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - League of Professional Theatre Training Programs, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - M (general), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Mazella Wire, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - J. McDonnell Coffee, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Modern Plates, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Mordecai, Ben, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Mututal Hardware, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Myer's Flower Shops, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - N (general), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - NCR, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - New England Newsclip, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - New Haven, City of, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - New Haven Info Magazine, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - New Haven Lumber, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - New Haven Travel, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - O (general), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Olive Electric, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Oxford Sales and Services, Co., 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - P (general), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - The Park Plaza, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Petty Cash, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Polyline Corp., 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Postage Meter and Stamps, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Postage-Business Reply Mail, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Postage, Bulk Mail, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Presto, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Production Arts, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Q (general), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - R (general), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Requests of Services, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Rose Band Textiles, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Russell Lumber, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - S (general), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Simon and Kurnin, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Sager Electric, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Senco Fasteners, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Shoreline Times, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - Slocum and Sons Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Russell Smith, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Sosensky's, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Sound Associates, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Speedway, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - S.S.D. and C., 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Stage Lighting Rental, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - T (general), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Tamsworth, Ltd., 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Telephone Service Requests, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Theatre Crafts Magazine, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Theatre Magic, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Theatre Techniques, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Ticket Craft, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Tower's Pharmacy, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Tyco, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Type House, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - U (general), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - V (general), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Vandais Lumber, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - W (general), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - S. Wolf and Sons, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Western Costume, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - X (general), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Y (general), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Yale Daily News, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Yale Printing Service, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - York Chevron, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Yale Medical School Copy Center, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Yale Lock Shop, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Yale Physical Plant, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Z (general), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 232)
  - 1984-1985
    - Casual Payroll F - O, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - Stock Request, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - Casual Forms P - Z, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 235)
    - 780B, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - 780A, B, C, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - Special Use Accounts, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - 780A, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - 780D, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - Facilities, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - 780C, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - 780R Inventory, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - Gifts, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - Grants, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - Endowment, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - Cash Receipts Journal, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Cash Receipts Journals, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - YQCC, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - Cash Receipts Journals, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - Limited Use Account, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 252)
    - Casual Payroll A-E, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 254)
  - 1986-1987
    - A (general), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 255)
    - Ace Sewing Machine, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 256)
    - Actors Equity Association, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 257)
    - Ads, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 258)
    - Advocate, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 259)
    - Alcone, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 260)
    - Almac Plastics, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 261)
    - AMA Products, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 262)
    - American Stage Lighting Rental, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 263)
    - Apartment 84 Howe Street # 300, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 264)
    - Apartment 84 Howe Street # 612, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 265)
    - Apartment 202 Park Street # 3, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 266)
    - Automatic Data Processing of New England, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 268)
    - B (general), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 269)
    - Bachman Distributors, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 270)
    - Baloo Enterprises, Ltd., 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 271)
    - B.M. Productions, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 272)
    - Bloom's, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 273)
    - Bridge Havenford Truck Sales, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 275)
    - Budget Rent-A-Car/Truck, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 276)
    - C (general), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 277)
    - The Camera Shops, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 278)
    - The Carpet Shops, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 279)
    - Centerville Lumber, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 281)
    - Chapel Wine, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 283)
    - Chapin and Bangs, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 284)
    - Charrette, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 285)
    - Charm's Hardware, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 286)
    - City of New Haven, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 287)
    - Coastal Tool Supply, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 290)
    - Cobb's Stationery, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 291)
    - Coe and Brown, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 292)
    - Colony Inn, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 293)
    - Commission on the Deaf, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 294)
    - Comp One, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 295)
    - Connecticut Bar and Restaurant, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 296)
    - Connecticut Fountain Syrup Co., 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 297)
    - Continental Lumber, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 298)
    - County Mailing Service, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 299)
    - Credit Card Usage, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 300)
    - Custom Food, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 301)
    - Cylinder Rent, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 302)
    - D (general), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 303)
    - Devoe and Reynolds, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 304)
    - Dichello Distributors, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 305)
    - Dining Halls (Request for Services), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 306)
    - Drama Productions, Inc. (First Quarter, 1987), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 307)
    - Drama Productions, Inc. (Second Quarter, 1987), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 308)
    - Drama Productions, Inc. (Third Quarter, 1987), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 309)
    - Drama Productions, Inc. (Fourth Quarter, 1986), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 310)
    - Duofast, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 311)
    - E (general), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 312)
    - Eagle Leasing, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 313)
    - F (general), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 316)
    - Federal Express, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 317)
    - S.Z. Field, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 318)
    - For Art's Sake, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 319)
    - Foxon Lumber, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 320)
    - G (general), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 323)
    - G and G Distributors, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 324)
    - Gnomon Copy, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 326)
    - Goodcopy, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 327)
    - Grand Light and Supply, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 328)
    - Great American Life Insurance, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 330)
    - Great Bear Spring, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - W. Grainger, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 332)
    - Greenberg and Hammer, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 333)
    - H (general), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 334)
    - Hartford, Cordage, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 336)
    - Harvard Business School, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 337)
    - Hatry Electronics, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 338)
    - Horowitz Brothers, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 340)
    - Hotel Duncan, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 341)
    - Howard Arnold, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 343)
    - Hull's Hobbies, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 344)
    - I (general), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 345)
    - Iggie's Saw Shop, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 346)
    - Industrial Safety Supply, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 347)
    - Instant Whip, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 348)
    - Insurance, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 349)
    - Internal Revenue Service, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 350)
    - Inventory, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 351)
    - J (general), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 352)
    - Jameco Electronics, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 353)
    - James Brown and Sons, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 354)
    - K (general), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 357)
    - Kaye's Art Shop, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 359)
    - Kelly Services, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 360)
    - Kinko's Copies, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 361)
    - Knox-Norton, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 362)
    - Koeing, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 363)
    - Kops-Monahan Travel, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 364)
    - L (general), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 365)
    - LaSalle Audio, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 366)
    - League of Professional Theatre Training Programs, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 367)
    - M (general), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - Maxco Enterprises, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 370)
    - J. McDonnell Coffee, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 374)
    - Milestar Entertainment, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 375)
    - Modern Plastics, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 376)
    - Mordecai, Benjamin, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 378)
    - Myer's Flower Shop, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 380)
    - N (general), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 382)
    - NCR, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 383)
    - New England Newsclip, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 384)
    - New Haven Register, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 385)
    - New Haven Travel, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 386)
    - O (general), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 387)
    - Olive Electric, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 388)
    - P (general), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 389)